<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<wannfeed version="1.0" archive="false">
	
	<item no="8">
		<header>Weekly WA: 13th July</header>
		<story id="13th July-1">
			<title>RSS Feed:</title>
			<desc><p>We've got a RSS feed running for all those who want to get updates that way; The feed is organised slightly differently with each story as an item so be warned. So here is the XML file link which you have to put into your feed reader: [http://feed43.com/wann-news.xml] this site will continue to be here and continue to include all the news we report.</p></desc>
		</story>
		<story id="13th July-2">
			<title>Island Creator Update:</title>
			<desc><p>As you have no doubt heard Bossa have updated the Island Creator to have even more easy-to-use cool tools for you you to create your island quicker. Thanks Bossa!</p></desc>
		</story>
		<story id="13th July-3">
			<title>Armada Drama:</title>
			<desc><p>So unfortunatly is looks like this might be a reoccurring title. However here is what happened. @vick-viper89 made a post (in reply to @louthinator) sugesting the Armada were in for fun and a roleplay faction not to tyranise the world, however this was later challenged by @louthinator saying that the Armada wouldnt be able to control their members and it would be a mess. While all this was going on @xerzie from the Free Skies Coallition jumped in defending the FSC from @louthinator on their decision to put a minimum member limit on players joining the FSC, though reassuring that they would help smaller alliances in need of help. In addition @oldrockgod came in from the Armada dissmissing @louthinator earlier claims. To summarise: We now these things: (1) The armada are the natural enemy to the establishment; the ying to the yang. (2) The FSC will be the main defenders of the peace (3) @meisterkeen is a great guy, no seriously his posts there were nice to read! And I'm not being paid to say that!; A group dedicated to seeing the safe gameplay of the smaller players and alliances. <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/forums/topic/bringing-alliances-together/">Here's the thread link</a></p></desc>
		</story>
		<story id="13th July-4">
			<title>Forum Watch:</title>
			<desc><p>Our favourite forum post this week is: <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/forums/topic/a-solution-to-cheaters-public-shaming/">A solution to cheaters: Public Shaming</a>; although not all agree with the proposition in Suggestions, it is certainly food for thought. Is it right or wrong? Thats why its our Forum Post of the Week.</p></desc>
		</story>
		<story id="13th July-5">
			<title>Alliance Watch:</title>
			<desc><p>Our Alliance this week is : <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/alliances/the-library/">The Library</a>, the crytpic league of nomads thats gonna chronicle everything. Yes, that's <strong>EVERYTHING</strong>. Though they allow alliance swapping they do not condone violence on other allainces; check their Codex stats on the WAAC!</p></desc>
		</story>
	</item>
	
	<item no="7">
		<header>Weekly WA: 6th July</header>
		<story id="7-1">
			<title>WANN: Update!</title>
			<desc><p>This will be one of the last of the techy updates posted here, I'll try to put more changelogs in commits in the github repo: <a href="https://github.com/W-A-N-N/W-A-N-N.github.io">LINK!</a> but we have semi-implemented a form for the WAAC and we're planning several more WA fan stuff!(e.g WASL, WART, WALN) Stay posted.</p></desc>
		</story>
		<story id="7-2">
			<title>Release date dilemma!</title>
			<desc><p>So, this week on the forum. @Strite started off with voicing his opinion saying Bossa should push the release date back. This apparently struck a unexpected chord witht the forum memebers many people jumping in there with agreements. Then to mount it up @darkhog started a "counter-thread" saying that Bossa will actually give accessibility to the 11th of July (to line up with the art competition deadline), however with the competition pushed back to the 31st of July that theory was debunked, or was it? go discuss <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/forums/topic/when-bossa-will-release-worlds-adrift-and-why-its-most-likely-july-11th/">11th July Theory</a> and <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/forums/topic/delay-the-game/">Strite's thread</a>. In addition, <span class="label label-warning">Luke Williams</span> jumped in and said that they want some more play tests before the initial release, maybe we'll get several before 11th July or alot alot between 2017, or perhaps Bossa have their own release date that they're right on track to. Get thinking! </p></desc>
		</story>
		<story id="7-3">
			<title>Alliance Watch:</title>
			<desc><p>Our alliance this week is: Oblitus est Spes, a faction that have already "begun campaigns of espionage on the major factions" so, these evil anarchists are coming for you. Though they've not called any enemies as of yet. See the <a href="https://w-a-n-n.github.io/waac">WAAC for more</a>. </p></desc>
		</story>
		<story id="7-4">
			<title>Forum Watch:</title>
			<desc><p>Throwing back several months our post of the forums this time is: <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/forums/topic/worlds-adrift-user-created-soundtrack/">Worlds Adrift User Created Soundtrack!</a> a brilliant thread for some WA themed songs, the youtube playlist is <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL1dpA29yznzsxSvxSGayJ-2jhONm4ntzI">here!</a>, enjoy some honestly amazing music!</p></desc>
		</story>
	</item>
	
	<item no="6">
		<header>Weekly WA: 29th June</header>
		<story id="6-1">
			<title>WANN: Update!</title>
			<desc><p>Just to let everyone know: The Worlds Adrift Alliance Codex (Beta) is live, this tool is based off the WAAC forum post as well as some other journalism. We also have completed the search feature on the main site! Finally, we're looking to add all sorts of WA helper features, so stay tuned!</p></desc>
		</story>
		<story id="6-2">
			<title>LORE OVERLOAD!</title>
			<desc><p>In the last blog post Bossa's lore department shipped another load of lore! It's seismic and a really good insight into the world of Foundation. Get theory-crafting!</p></desc>
		</story>
		<story id="6-3">
			<title>Alliance Watch:</title>
			<desc><p>Our alliance this week is: RageQuit! also on our WAAC, they're the 'wildcard' of the WA alliances, so watch your backs!</p></desc>
		</story>
		<story id="6-4">
			<title>Forum Watch:</title>
			<desc><p>This weeks forum topic is: <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/forums/topic/around-the-world-in-80-days/">Around the World in 80 days</a>. A topic all about races and regattas in the Worlds Adrift universe. We personally think that we cant wait to get filming the sports! And its a great idea and we should all be lining up to take part!</p></desc>
		</story>
	</item>
	
	<item no="5">
		<header>Weekly WA: 22nd June</header>
		<story id="5-1">
			<title>WANN! The future!</title>
			<desc><p>This being our 1st month as WANN; We just wanted to say THANK YOU! to Bossa and the players who read this site and will read this site. We want to become the No.1 source for in-game news, events and battles! We also have some tantalisingly good features coming up, eg. A mailto so you never miss a update; an Alliance codex! as well as some other stuff. Thanks again to all the players as we continue on this path to the WA release!</p></desc>
		</story>
		<story id="5-2">
			<title>Forum Watch:</title>
			<desc><p>This week our favourite forum post is: The <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/fourms/topic/schematic-limit-rebalance-suggestion/">Schematic Limit Rebalance Suggestion</a>! Which discusses the way in-game ship schematics work!</p></desc>
		</story>
		<story id="5-3">
			<title>Alliance Watch:</title>
			<desc><p>This weeks Piratin' alliance is "the Dread Pirates : Gold, Gore, and Glory" we wont mention the misplaced comma before the "and" in case they come and pillage our HQ! These pirates aren't your normal Pirates, no. They strike fear into the hearts of the Top Dogs on the ranking! Taking on: RageQuit, Sky Drifters and the powerhouse Sky Armada!</p></desc>
		</story>
	</item>
	
	<item no="4">
		<header>Weekly WA: 15th June</header>
		<story id="4-1">
			<title>GAME UPDATE!</title>
			<desc>
				<p>The blog this week gives us an insight into the modular mechanics in Worlds Adrift! <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/blog/modular-mechanics/">Look here!</a> As well as showing us some amazing designs of the cannons, wings and engines to put on our Sky Ships.</p>
			</desc>
		</story>
		<story id="4-2">
			<title>Feature Spotlight!</title>
			<desc>
				<p>For those players who missed it, this weeks favourite feature is: Player Spawning! Bossa said <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/forums/topic/spawn-points/#post-3301">here</a> that players will be spawned in regions deemed 'safe' from other players. Though it is good to note that this system won't be perfect and might end up in early game skirmishes.</p>
			</desc>
		</story>
		<story id="4-3">
			<title>Forum Watch:</title>
			<desc>
				<p>Check out the <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/forums/topic/discord-server-for-worlds-adrift/">Discord Server</a> to chat about the game with other like-minded people on Discord!</p>
			</desc>
		</story>
		<story id="4-4">
			<title>Alliance Watch:</title>
			<desc>
				<p>This weeks alliance is: <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/alliances/ryder/">Ryder</a>,  who are a loose coalition of ships with a Chaotic Neutral alignment, Watch out!</p>
			</desc>
		</story>
	</item>
  
  <item no="3">
	<header>Weekly WA: 8th June</header>
	<story id="3-1">
	<title>Grammar drama: Part 2</title>
	<desc>
		<p>
	@Vick-viper89 responded to the Drifters challenge by reassuring their population-based superiority in the Creative Writing thread as well as confirming the GSA's stance on Piracy!
	</p>
	</desc>
	</story>
	<story id="3-2">
	<title>Alliance Watch</title>
	<desc>
		<p>
	We went through the top 2 Alliance pages and picked our favourites, here we go:
	Our alliance of the week is <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/alliances/the-glorious-sky-armada/">The Glorious Sky Armada</a>, for they're currently supreme population and dedication to their cause. They seek to unite the world under their one banner!
	</p>
	</desc>
	</story>
	<story id="3-3">
	<title>Forum Watch</title>
	<desc>
		<p>
	We went through mounds of General Discussion and Suggestions and Creative Writing and got our fave post from all time!
	This week its: <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/forums/topic/founder-packs-what-do-we-want-to-see/">Founders Packs</a>!!! Check it out on General.
	</p>
	</desc>
	</story>
</item>

<item no="2" for="everyone">
  <header>Weekly WA: 1st June</header>
  <story id="2-1">
    <title>Grammar Drama</title>
  <desc>
  	<p>
    Sky Drifter @Greenjuice has openly criticised the Armada's chronicler for his Creative Writing piece pointing out many grammatical flaws, The Armada have responded pointing out their Militaristic superiority in the situation. Nice move @Vick-Viper89
  </p>
  </desc>
  </story>
  <story id="2-2">
    <title>Forum Watch</title>
    <desc>
    	<p>
      This weeks forum topic spotlight goes to Blog Post 'In Search of Utopia' Featuring some lovely lore and background on the World Foundation, recommended for all. Enjoy!
    	</p>
    </desc>
  </story>
</item>

<item no="1" for="everyone">
  <header>LIVE!</header>
  <story id="1-1">
  <title>GOOOOOD MOOOORNIIING WOOOORLDS AAADRIFT</title>
  <desc><p>  We've gone live!! From fleet v fleet battles to a Propaganda war, we've got you covered, no more shall the players be in the dark, welcome to the light!</p></desc>
  </story>
</item>
</wannfeed>
