<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<wannfeed version="1.0" archive="false">
  
  <item no="3">
	<header>Weekly WA: 8th June</header>
	<story>
	<title>Grammar drama: Part 2</title>
	<desc>
		<p>
	@Vick-viper89 responded to the Drifters challenge by reassuring their population-based superiority in the Creative Writing thread as well as confirming the GSA's stance on Piracy!
	</p>
	</desc>
	</story>
	<story>
	<title>Alliance Watch</title>
	<desc>
		<p>
	We went through the top 2 Alliance pages and picked our favourites, here we go:
	Our alliance of the week is <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/alliances/the-glorious-sky-armada/">The Glorious Sky Armada</a>, for they're currently supreme population and dedication to their cause. They seek to unite the world under their one banner!
	</p>
	</desc>
	</story>
	<story>
	<title>Forum Watch</title>
	<desc>
		<p>
	We went through mounds of General Discussion and Suggestions and Creative Writing and got our fave post from all time!
	This week its: <a href="https://www.worldsadrift.com/forums/topic/founder-packs-what-do-we-want-to-see/">Founders Packs</a>!!! Check it out on General.
	</p>
	</desc>
	</story>
</item>

<item no="2" for="everyone">
  <header>Weekly WA: 1st June</header>
  <story>
    <title>Grammar Drama</title>
  <desc>
  	<p>
    Sky Drifter @Greenjuice has openly criticised the Armada's chronicler for his Creative Writing piece pointing out many grammatical flaws, The Armada have responded pointing out their Militaristic superiority in the situation. Nice move @Vick-Viper89
  </p>
  </desc>
  </story>
  <story>
    <title>Forum Watch</title>
    <desc>
    	<p>
      This weeks forum topic spotlight goes to Blog Post 'In Search of Utopia' Featuring some lovely lore and background on the World Foundation, recommended for all. Enjoy!
    	</p>
    </desc>
  </story>
</item>

<item no="1" for="everyone">
  <header>LIVE!</header>
  <story>
  <title>GOOOOOD MOOOORNIIING WOOOORLDS AAADRIFT</title>
  <desc><p>  We've gone live!! From fleet v fleet battles to a Propaganda war, we've got you covered, no more shall the players be in the dark, welcome to the light!</p></desc>
  </story>
</item>
</wannfeed>
